Hello everyone, this is Niyalee Cole Joy.
This time, we're going to talk about 40 highlights of Ozora Bunt's music video.
This time, I'd like to talk about the music video of our 6th song "Ozora Bunt", including behind-the-scenes stories and highlights.
I'm going to talk a lot about the highlights of the music video.
What do you think?
This is the first time you've seen something like this on Youtube.
I've never seen anything like this before on youtube.
So let's make it the 6th song.
Yes, make it the 6th song.
I don't even know what the right answer is.
By the way, Ayumi was in the center this time.
How was the shooting?
Well, the weather forecast was for rain on the day of the mv shoot, so I wasn't sure if the weather would be okay.
I was wondering if the weather would be fine, but it turned out to be fine on the day.
It was a really nice shoot.
It was a big sky.
And the thunderstorm.
There was a lyric in the song, "Looking up at the blue sky.
It was raining really hard.
Yeah, it was a real mess.
Well, thank goodness Nya Joy was there to see us.
Okay, let's get to it.
If you have a point you'd like to make, just hit the ping pong button on your hand and let's talk about it.
Let's get on with it.
Please do.
Intro.
Oh, yes.
Mr. Center.
One, one, one, please.
You see this scene here with all these chairs lined up in a row?
I'm sitting in the middle.
And next to you, a regular person? An old man sits next to me.
At this moment...
He probably didn't understand that we were filming.
The staff told him several times not to sit here, but he couldn't hear them.
But the old man didn't seem to hear.The old man couldn't hear him.
Like, "Yes.
He kept saying, "What?
It was funny.
It's so peaceful.
I was just stretching.
I have a question. I have a question.
This is right before the plane takes off.
Did you wait to shoot this?
Yeah, I think I waited.
Wait? You don't remember.
I don't remember.
We took a lot of pictures.
I'm sure he's timing his shots.
That's amazing.
It's amazing that you can see the plane from the first shot.
That's great.
Don't ever push me again.
Don't push me.
Okay, let's move on.
Yes, please.
You had three seconds.
That's right.
Oh!
This!
The contents of this letter... it's as if Ayumi's mom wrote it.
It's really moving me.
What? What was that?
Didn't you feel like crying?
I was so moved.
But it's not from your real mom.
Oh, no.
There was a theory that Ayumi's real mom was in the show.
Yes, she was.
That's true.
I saw a comment that Sashiwa-san was on the show.
What? What? What?What? Huh? Huh?
Someone commented that your mother's profile looked like Sashiwa-san.
Huh?
There was a comment that...
What? That's amazing.
It was Sashi Awa?
Maybe.
Maybe...
What if...
What? Too gorgeous!
Stop again.
Okay, hey, hey, hey.
Let's take a look.
What? Oh, my God.
Wow.
Yes. Ayumi's coordinate is great!
Ayumi's sporty coordinate is very nice.
I can tell.
Properly Ayumi, there is a person who identifies this outfit,
I'd like to see it at the online story meeting. Like, I bought it.
Good night.
A hat, sandals...
Sandals?
I don't have any right now.
Let's see the sandals.
I'm sure we'll see the whole body.
I'll come back next time.
Please do.
Don't start with me, apparently.
A long raid stage?
Sure thing.
I like this one.
I like the dance.
It's good.
Ayumi!
Is that a monitor behind here?
The logo of Nearly Equal Juice on the monitor?
Yes, it's good.Yeah.
What flight would you normally take? What flight, what destination, what flight, what flight,
It's like Near Juice jacked it up.
When you go to an airport, there are usually a lot of people there.
I was amazed that for the first time, I was able to enter a part of the airport with just Near Juice, or rather, with just such people,
You never get to do that in your life.
It was a great experience.
I was so excited.
I'm looking forward to it.
Please enjoy.
Please do.
Thank you for catching me as usual, Sakira-kun!
Ayumi, I just wanted to push it where I thought it would stop.
That kind of thing?
Everyone's anti-aircraft.
Mitsuki was flying so fast.
Wait, wait.
Isn't it like a heart?
They all look like this.
Ayumi is good in the group. She seems to be good at it.
Mitsuki's good at jumping while airborne.
That's why she'll be on top even if I land on her.
That's it? I think she's up there.
That's why this was the highlight.
It was amazing during the lesson.
One of them had a lot of time in the air.
He was here the whole time.
That's for sure.
Here we go.
Is he dead?
Is he being killed?
You're so cute!
So cute!
It's so cute!
And the cloud thingy in the back, and the wall.
I love the wall. The sky.
Oh, there's Julie.
Bye Ann.Vian.
I like this one.
Smile.
I'm trainin'.
I like this one!
I love the song. I love it!
Song? Song?
Song? No, no, no.
You know what it's like here? You're on your phone, and you're communicating with each other.
It's so real, you know?
The realness of the feeling that you're really on your way.
I don't know how Ayumi was feeling when she flew in, but...
I'm just thinking about it and I'm moved.
It's nice.
I like that there is a stairway to the top, too.
Realistic, indeed.
It's really nice.
Oh, wait, what's this dress-up?
I can never tell with this tote dress-up.
I want to make these matching.
I want to make specific totes for each other.
The free ones?
Oh, free tote?
If you're an Ayumi fan, you'll get a pink one.
Pink.
Matching tote.
But this isn't my phone.
Oh, I see.
That's right.
But...
Oh, that's right.
It's my phone.
Here.
Oh, this one.
That's good.
Shall we go?
Ayumi, that's good.
Yes, it's good.All right.
Ooh.
Everybody's dancing.
I wiped my tears.
You looked so dazzled.
I got so dizzy.
You know what I'm saying?
Where is it?
I don't know, on the roof of some airport?
I don't know.
I don't know. It's a different coat.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't know.
You're right. I don't see a lot of people.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
This is it.
Great! There it is!
Lame lame lame! Please, maybe she can speak for me.
Ayumi's expression is too cute.
Ayumi tilting her head. Yes, really good.
I'll keep looking at it. You're always telling me that.
You know... basically... in this music video... there's a lot of Ayumi's... you know... drama scenes.
There's a lot of drama scenes in her music videos... and I've taken the liberty of taking scans of them.
Really?
You're the type of person who takes pictures.
I want to be scrubbed!
I've never heard of that before.
I'm so happy.
It's so cute.
I'm sure everyone here really thinks so... and there's been a lot of comments about it.
Yeah, Ayumi.
Ayumi. She's really cute.
but... it's a bit of a misnomer... it's like the ramen isn't good.
I mean it's not that it's not good... it's just that compared to the local tonkotsu ramen it's not quite the same.
but it was delicious. We ate the whole thing.
I love it!
I ate it!I ate.
Ew!
I'm glad the pork bone ramen came along to raise the bar.
That's all I have to say.
I joined the studio for the first time
of all time.
Yes, yes, yes.
I'm sorry, I didn't press the button.
The costumes...
There are costumes of Ricoeur Joy and Balate Frasier.
I think they're emo.
Go on.
Go ahead.
Oh, I don't like this.
That, uh, that's okay.
Oh, I don't like it there.
No, no, no, no.
What is this? Something bitter.
I heard something about recording.
I heard that you sang this one more time with your hands clasped together
I heard that he sang it with his hands clasped together.
It's in the song, too.
And the expression on her face...
Ai-chan's feelings are on her face.
I love it.
Singing is acting, right?
So cool!
Well, then, please.
Oh, oh, oh, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no.
You know, this scene right here, it's, uh...
Everyone's so happy.
Nia, you know, we've been together for a little over a year.
We've been together for two years now.
But in this music video, they've just formed
It's a scene where she says "I'm looking forward to working with you from now on.
It's a scene where we say hello for the first time.It's a scene from one of the first meet and greets.
Everyone is trying a little too hard to be nice
like it's nice to meet you.
Please take a look.
It was difficult, wasn't it?
It was difficult.
Ayumi was like, "We're a pair.
That's right.
Like, "Ayumi, it's okay.
Can you move it a little?
Move it a little?
Around here.
Here... here...
It's like a making-of camera.
This is so realistic.
Yes, it is.
In the beginning, there was a making-of.
When we first met.
It's amazing how they're in the making of the film.
You're right.
It's really from our point of view during the shoot.
There's never a making-of featurette.
I'm looking forward to it.
That's true.
When we're really filming, it's from our point of view.
I'm looking forward to seeing the making of.
I'm looking forward to it.
Ayumi.
This one.
I like this.
Ayumi Dokidoki
When we were doing this...
Let's all stand in a row here.
Ayumi was here.
We were all looking at her.
And the moment she did this, I thought, "Oh, she's so cute.
Everyone was reacting a little bit.
That there were a lot of things that weren't on the screen.I've noticed that a lot of them don't show up.
When you're acting nervous...
Like this.
In the background.
It's good to have your hands in the right position.
You're right. Keep your hands together.
When we get nervous, we do this too.
Instead of the engine, we do this.
Instead of an engine, we do this.
Ta-da!
This is too much!
Let's go next time.
Let's go next.
Here we go.
This is it.
Alice... she said she wasn't good at the lip scene at the beginning.
She said she wasn't good at lipstick scenes.
I was struggling so hard.
Yeah, and the beret is cute.
It's cute.
And she can even do the hand gestures.
And he even stuck his teeth out.
That's amazing.
It's like a parent's perspective, isn't it?
It's the 6th song.
You've done this song six times.
It's all coming out.
I love the visuals.
She's so cute.
It's refreshing.
She's cute.
Cute.
Nice. Nice.
Let's take a picture.
I love the way they're all flirting.
I love it.
I love this video.
It's like it's gonna be in a music video.I didn't film it as if I was going to be in a music video.
I didn't film it like I wanted to be in the music video.
I was just taking pictures in my natural state.
I thought it was just a normal photo shoot.
But first...
Wait a minute.
This is not good.
What kind of pose is this?
We were going to do something together.
We're going to do something together.
I don't know how to pose.
I don't know what to do.
I said, "Let's do something like this.
I said, "Let's do something like that.
But the moment he said that, I just laughed.
So that's where you are.
You're in Pauline Love?
I see.
So that's why you're smiling.
You're smiling a lot.
She's smiling.
You're so cute.
That's a good wink.
Good wink.
You're going for it.
The review short...
Oh, my God.
He's got a really nice wiggle.
Maybe... maybe if you winked.
I think if I winked, it would look like I was really glancing at a fan.
I'm going to feel like I'm being targeted.
If you ever feel like you've been targeted...
I'd like you to know that it was a wink.
Don't look away from us.
This pose.
This time.
With the sky in focus.
It's not that bad.It's pretty much not this.
And the chorus, too, with the big sky pinto.
So it's kind of a symbolic pose.
I think it's a symbolic pose.
It's an airplane.
Wings?
You should try to imitate it.
and try it out!
Please make this pose popular!
Please make it popular!
What do you think?
Ah!
It looks good on you.
I did it twice.
What's this place?
At the beginning of the second chorus.
I don't know if you can see the dance.
That was the hardest part of the song.
In the original dance song.
In the dance.
How do you describe the choreography?
Yes, yes, yes.
It's so detailed, and we all had to practice together.
We practiced.
Even right before the show.
I said, "What should we do?
And they didn't use it.
You're right, you're right.
Please pay attention to the chorus.
1414All of them are different, aren't they?
The choreography is so beautiful, isn't it?
I love it!
Check out the chorus!
Oh, there it is!
Here it is!
Wait!Wait.
Why isn't he smiling?
I'm not looking at you like that.
This scene was difficult.
Amin was nervous.
Like, "How about a little more like this?
Amin is more experienced.
That's the setup.
It was a setup.
Aimin's so good at it, he never laughs.
That's why Aimin...
I'm not going to laugh.
It was difficult.
Oh, we're the same.
Yes, I'll get it.
Oh, I'll get it.
It's a little bit too late.
It's just this one day when you're smiling...
I'll be here.
They're all on my shoulders like this.
I don't know how to say it, but...
During rehearsal
Aimin was kind of mocking me when we were rehearsing
I felt her posture
I really felt her posture.
It was my favorite part of the rehearsal.
It was my favorite part.
This lever is so easy to see.
You do that every time, don't you?
You know, right here.
Julie...
There's something different about her.
Julie is always...
She's always...
She's so serious.
She was.There she is.
I see Julie singing pretentiously.
I want to look good.
I can totally understand.
Julie's kind of...
She's always joking around, and... she's so energetic.
There's such a big difference in temperature.
It's so funny.
This lever says it all.
This face tells the story.
Everything.
He's not grinning.
Alice is curious, too... and she's looking at him.
Rico!
She's peeking in, isn't she?
Julie, you're good with expressions, aren't you?
She's got a great expression, doesn't she?
Like that sad expression.
I got a compliment.
I have to give this one a high rating.
It's going to be on the air forever.
Thank you very much.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
May I?
This, uh, this is not it.
Ki-chan!
It's something, Ki-chan, isn't it?
This is, you know, conscious.
Well, I don't know, they didn't say anything else.
Oh, really?
I haven't been told that I'm Ki-chan anymore.
You know me.
You just pinpointed it,
You pinpointed it to Ki-chan in your comment,
Ayumi's winning,
Yes, I'm winning.
Ki-chan,You know, Kii,
That parakeet,
Like this,
It's the same, you know.
It's my pet.
So cute.
Ah!
Korra's face is so cute when she's spinning.
It's so cute.
I love it.
Back.
Oh, I love this!
A nago.
We're on the same course.
Dumplings?
Dumplings are fast! So fast!
Rare! So rare!
It's really cute.
It's like a loungewear.
It's like a loungewear,
The loose-fitting hoodie and the bun,
And also, it's like I just moved to Tokyo and made my first pancake all by myself,
It's like I burnt the first pancake I made when I first moved to Tokyo,
It was really adorable.
It's a great setting, isn't it?
It's really good.
Really?
Too strong, now.
I think it's okay if I press it too hard here, I won't destroy it.
I think it's okay,
Ayumi came out with her head tilted up,
I can really see her expression with the bun over here,
Ayumi, I love Ayumi with the tilted neck.
That's all.
It's so nice, isn't it?
It's great because it comes out from here.
One second.
Oh, no!Oh, no!
Ayumi is cute even from this angle.
But to a kitten,
Just by looking at this screen,
I feel like a kitten.
I feel like Ayumi picked me up.
When I see this,
I am a kitten, and Ayumi picked me up,
I can have a pseudo-experience that I am a kitten and Ayumi picked me up.
It's really great, isn't it?
A good guy's day.
That happens often.
Oh, this!
I love this Ayumi.
It's nice.
It's definitely salted chestnuts.
That's salted chestnuts, right?
Really.
I wonder if my interpretation is correct.
I don't know, but I'm imagining it,
It's kind of nice, isn't it?
Ayumi is getting all these salted chestnuts.
You know what I mean?
Ayumi's cute and she's getting salted chestnuts,
She's loved by her parents.
She's so cute.
Do you get it?
You really are a fan, aren't you?
But you're the only one who can say that.
No, he's really cute.
Oh, oh, oh, now.
Riddle.
It's got the answer.
Aren't you tired? You should get some rest once in a while.
Oh, wait.
I like the pictographs.
I like the pictograms.
Dad says he's rooting for you.Dad said he's rooting for you, too.
That's nice.
If you send your parents,
I wonder if it's too rich.
That's really sweet.
Oh, that's nice.
Oh.
Hey.
Oh, wow.
Oh, nice.
It's really like the making of, like, here,
It's like the camera's really in the making of.
Here?
Oh, it's much funnier.
Hey, good mood, no.
You're funny all the time.
What's with the face?
This is really the making of, you know, the making of, like, with the camera in the background.
I'm kind of in the making-of,
That's really what it looks like.
That's really it.
I didn't know when I had the camera.
We were in the middle of the story,
It was like we were shooting a music video for the first time.
So when the camera guy came,
I didn't know if I should talk about it or not.
I don't know if I should talk about it,
I didn't know if it was me who was shooting this music video for the first time, or if it was the real Ozawami.
I didn't know if it was me or not,
I didn't know who I was.
But, you know,
And then, you know, we all kind of, you know,
I was just kind of in a relationship, you know, something,
I remember when we made a video, you know, like an impression.
I don't know what to do,
the looks on everyone's faces, like they didn't know what to do.
It was so funny,
But still, Yuka-chan, was it?Still, you know, Yuka-chan, wasn't it?
She was talking.
She was talking like it was her first time,
Oh, that was so funny.
And this time, too, she was like, "UEC.
I said, "Oh, is this how you do it? I said, "Oh, you do it like this?
I said, "Oh, you're standing in the wrong position on purpose,
Oh, this way? Like, "Oh, this way?
It was the kind of thing you don't know how to do.
I didn't know him at all.
It was fun.
It's nice, isn't it?
Oh, it was in the back.
Oh, oh, oh, oh,
Ah, here it is.
Ayumi's thumping again.
Is this a habit?
You didn't pair this.
What is this?
I thought so myself.
So cute!
There was a theory that this might be Shaara, who was mentioned earlier.
Here it is.
It's here.
I saw that in the comments section quite a bit.
Oops.
It's just as it is.
Oh, no.
This is not Shaara.
No, it's not.
I'll continue what I was saying.
There was a theory that Ayumi's real mother was here.
Yes, it was.
It's out?
That's not true.
Of course not.
That's as expected.
You're right.As you'd expect.
But I met this mother when we were shooting Hot Gickeys in her apartment.
She was putting a lot of emotion into it, and she was concentrating on doing a mental toilet for this performance.
So the crew had to shoot in a quiet whisper.
That's right.
Silent hot chickie.
Quiet now.
We did it like this.
We did it with a scene.
I'm so nervous.
I'm also nervous about doing it in a jiffy.
That's right.
That's terrible.
I was by myself.
I wasn't a member.
That's right.
I didn't know that.
We're flying high!
Yes!
The choreography here is really hard!
It's been quite a while since we choreographed it, but it's hard.
I don't know if I'm doing it well yet.
I'm not sure if I'm doing it well yet,
I have to keep up with the sound, but I can't. I can't move my body as I want,
I know I shouldn't lag behind, but I can't get my body to move as I want it to,
This is something we all struggle with every time we go to bed.
It's difficult.
Left, right?
Left, right, left, right.
Around here?
Pee.
I have to pee.
Oh, no.
Bridge of the Air Force
Yes! This is the Bridge of the Supreme Commander of the Air Force here,
Um, the amount of Ayumi and Mai moving around on this side is very difficult,Um, the amount of movement of Ayumi and Mai on this side is very difficult,
Whenever the scene here comes,
I hope you'll think, "You did a great job.
I've said it many times,
I've told you many times... but here in SNS, the choreography is wrong.
What? I've been gut-assaulted.
That's for sure.
The sky!
That's right.
The Air Force.
And they didn't stop.
I didn't notice it until now.
But wait, isn't that a Newari colo pose?
What? No, it's not.
No, right?
Is it that dexterous?
No, it's just now,
But..,
I'm too eager to spread Miyagi.
That's great.
You're going for it in a very forward way.
I don't know, I can't tell.
I don't know.
We took a lot of pictures here, didn't we?
We took a lot of pictures here.
Why did you take it here?
Isn't this a good pattern? Here.
Was it good?
One shot.
Ayumi's here already, the last sunny day.
I feel the sky
Like we're going forward.
She's fluttering with the wind.
And her hair's also fluttering.
And her ribbon...
It's kind of sheer.
It's a nice touch.
It's nice.That's nice.
You have a beautiful smile.
No, but it was dazzling.
It was definitely glaring.
There it is.
This is a personal thing.
Ayumi has a cool image among fans, right?
Ayumi is so funny when she talks with us backstage.
She's really funny.
I think she's the funniest person I've ever met in my life.
I think she's funny.
She has the best sense of words.
And I have an image of him smiling.
That's why cool expressions are often used.
I'm glad that Ayumi's super smile is still there.
It's interesting.
Watch me.
Yes, I'm watching!
Yes!
I'm watching! I'm watching!
I'm watching!
You don't have to tell me, I'm watching!
I really like the way your mom is looking at you!
Your mom has beautiful hands!
When we were shooting this lip-tune shoot, everyone could see it, you know?
When they do the hearts and cute poses, it gets a big reaction.
It was so exciting here! It was like a gala!
They were so excited, they were like "wow"!
But he was in good spirits.
It was great to see you guys.
It was fun to see you guys.
Yeah, it was.
Aah! There it is!
I feel like it's all over the place.
Oh!
I'm going to make a deposit.I'm going to backfill it.
When I worked in this costume
When I was working in this costume
I told the photographer
I told the photographer that I could put the pockets
If you can put it away, I'd like you to put it away.
I was like, "If you can put it away, I'd like you to put it away.
But the manager said
Ah! This is the costume!
Sometimes, you know, they have shorts...
You know, the ones that come out of the inside pocket.
I guess he thought it was like that.
That's funny.
Connor is feeling this one first.
He feels it.
And Leno's feeling it, too.
He's touching his eyes to his hands.
That's too funny.
It's hard to stop dancing when you're dancing.
That's true.
Let's do it.
Ready?
There's more.
Yes!
Oh! I took a little too many pictures.
I'm supposed to take pictures here.
It's a normal high-five, but it's been used to my heart's content.
That's true.
But... you know... we took a picture of you dancing before.
It was after we took some of it, so it was really...
When we were dancing, everyone was in sync.
It was like, "Yay, it's over!
That's true.
And when I said it was over, they were like, "Let's do it again.
Oh, it wasn't over.
That's just how it was, just a little bit of excitement.
That's the real making of.
Please check.Please confirm.
Thank you for your hard work
How was the shooting today?
Yes, sir.
It's still there.
Behind Aimee.
Aimee, Momochan and Yuuka.
And Julie.
These four are really just themselves.
Tell them it's okay, it's not going to be on the screen.
"Let's take a picture here. Or something.
"Let's take a picture here.
If you're taking pictures, you're in the picture.
It's hard to get a picture of the staff.
I don't mean the epistolary staff members.
It's just a lot of the staff that are always there for us.
You know that upstairs thing over there?
That's where the real ones are all the time.
They were watching over the real Tobias Tenders and stuff.
I was so happy that they were watching over us.
And I glanced up once.
And they were clapping for me.
I was so happy.
I'm so happy.
I can do my best.
It's so great!
It was a lot of fun.
Finished
It was fun
It's over
I'm done watching until the end.
We saw a lot, didn't we?
What did you think of the sights?
There were a lot of really good parts.
I think I'm not done yet.
Me too.
It was really high, wasn't it?That was so expensive.
I'm so happy.
I'm glad to see you enjoying yourself.
Shu-shu, you were so excited like a relative of mine.
He was talking all the time.
There were so many things to praise.
I heard a lot of behind-the-scenes stories about Ayumi's shooting by herself.
I didn't know her at all.
I think today was the first time I could talk to her.
I'm glad.
Please give us a closing speech by Ayumi, the center of the show.
I don't know if I can close it well.
This song is about supporting those who leave their hometowns to pursue their dreams.
Please listen to it as much as you can, thinking of your loved ones.
That's all for now, this is Joy from IARICO!
Bye bye!
This is Joy from Ialyco.